<Namespace Name="System.Net.PeerToPeer">
  <Metadata><Meta Name="ms.openlocfilehash" Value="320f5d11742848ae51a1bbb18f46ae6b439a5235" /><Meta Name="ms.sourcegitcommit" Value="397961a0164281b579f68064c3bb66c071f374d9" /><Meta Name="ms.translationtype" Value="MT" /><Meta Name="ms.contentlocale" Value="zh-CN" /><Meta Name="ms.lasthandoff" Value="07/14/2020" /><Meta Name="ms.locfileid" Value="64279550" /></Metadata><Docs>
    <summary><span data-ttu-id="b7bff-101"><see cref="N:System.Net.PeerToPeer" /> 命名空间提供了对等网络功能的访问权。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="b7bff-101">The <see cref="N:System.Net.PeerToPeer" /> namespace provides access to peer networking functionality.</span></span></summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="b7bff-102">对等互连和解析标识符的方式在暂时性连接上非常复杂，并且无法访问域名系统（DNS）等地址记录。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="b7bff-102">How peers discover each other and resolve identifiers is complicated by transient connectivity and the lack of access to address records such as the Domain Name System (DNS).</span></span>  <span data-ttu-id="b7bff-103">Windows 对等基础结构解决了名解析和名为 PNRP 的对等发现方案的这一问题。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="b7bff-103">The Windows Peer-to-Peer Infrastructure solves this problem with a name resolution and peer discovery scheme called PNRP.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="b7bff-104">对等名称解析协议（PNRP）为对等网络提供名称解析机制。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="b7bff-104">Peer Name Resolution Protocol (PNRP) provides a name resolution mechanism for peer-to-peer networks.</span></span>  <span data-ttu-id="b7bff-105">PNRP 旨在以完全对等的方式将名称解析为网络 <xref:System.Net.IPEndPoint> 。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="b7bff-105">PNRP is designed to resolve a name to a network <xref:System.Net.IPEndPoint> in a completely peer-to-peer manner.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="b7bff-106">命名空间类中提供了基本 PNRP 功能 <xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer> 。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="b7bff-106">Basic PNRP functionality is provided in the <xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer> namespace classes.</span></span>  <span data-ttu-id="b7bff-107">它们提供了创建对等方并将其注册到对等方的功能 <xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Cloud> 。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="b7bff-107">They provide the ability to create a peer and register it in a <xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Cloud> of peers.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="b7bff-108">它们还提供将解析 <xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.PeerName> 为其网络终结点、TCP 端口、云或其他地址标识符的功能。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="b7bff-108">They also provide the ability to resolve a <xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.PeerName> to its network endpoint, TCP port, cloud, or other address identifier(s).</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="b7bff-109">命名空间中提供对等网络的高级功能 <xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Collaboration> 。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="b7bff-109">Advanced functionality for peer-to-peer networking is provided in the <xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Collaboration> namespace.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="b7bff-110">在 Windows Vista 中，PNRP 作为一项按应用程序的要求启动的服务。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="b7bff-110">In Windows Vista, PNRP ships as a service that is started on demand by applications.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="b7bff-111">此外，如果应用程序或用户希望发布用于远程连接和通信的计算机名称，则会有一个 PNRP 计算机注册服务可由应用程序或用户手动启用。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="b7bff-111">In addition, there is a PNRP machine registration service that can be manually enabled by applications or users if they want to publish machine names for remote connections and communications.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="b7bff-112">PNRP 版本1包含在 Windows XP Service Pack 2 （SP2）、Windows XP Professional x64 Edition 和 windows xp Service Pack 1 （SP1）和 Windows XP 的高级网络包中。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="b7bff-112">PNRP version 1 was included in Windows XP Service Pack 2 (SP2), Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, and Windows XP with Service Pack 1 (SP1) and the Advanced Networking Pack for Windows XP.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="b7bff-113">此外，如果在发布计算机名称以进行远程连接和通信时，应用程序/用户可以手动启用 PNRP 计算机注册服务。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="b7bff-113">In addition, there is a PNRP machine registration service which can be manually enabled by applications/users if there is interest in publishing machine names for remote connection and communication.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
    <altmember cref="N:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Collaboration" />
  </Docs>
</Namespace>